W.A.C. Bennett fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Post-Premier subject files, 1972 - 1978; F-55-15; 1.38 m of textual records
  - Financial Information - Newsletters, printed material, 1975; F-55-15-0-0-45 (Archival box - standard 55-13)
  - Financial Information - Articles, newsletters, pamphlets, letters, 1975; F-55-15-0-0-46 (Archival box - standard 55-13)
  - Financial Information - Newsletters, printed material, 1975; F-55-15-0-0-47 (Archival box - standard 55-13)
  - Financial Information - Newsletters, pamphlets, 1975; F-55-15-0-0-48 (Archival box - standard 55-13)
  - General Correspondence - Letters, invitations. Letters from: A.T. Harrison, W.T. Armstrong, Betty Tessard, Allan Fotheringham, A.E. Olson, 1975; F-55-15-0-0-49 (Archival box - standard 55-13)
  - General Correspondence - Letters, invitations. Letters from: Mary Lang, Mrs. David Kaiser, Clarence Wilson, R.D. Rann, R.R. Jeffels, R.E. Sutherland, William Clancey, John R. Hecht, 1975; F-55-15-0-0-50 (Archival box - standard 55-13)
  - General Correspondence - Letters, printed material. Letters from: Ira M. Gomfar, Grace McCarthy, William Clancey, K. McClarep, Ronald B. Worley, Jan Corba, Frank Carson, Robert W. Bonner, A.N. Blicq, Margaret L. Murray, Gary Bannerman, 1975; F-55-15-0-0-51 (Archival box - standard 55-13)
  - General Correspondence - Letters, invitations, printed material. Letters from: Harry C.J. Phillips, Chris S. Skarvig, Lorraine Thomson, K.L. Morton, Ronald B. Worley, Irene Moore, George A. Wilkinson, L. Curtis, Pat N. Goode, H.R. MacMillan, 1975; F-55-15-0-0-52 (Archival box - standard 55-13)
  - General Correspondence - Letters. Letters from: Ray G. Williston, Grace McCarthy, John R. Hecht, John N. Turner, Karen Sleeman, Anna A. Hugel, Ronald B. Worley, May Bennett, Mike Hartwick, 1975; F-55-15-0-0-53 (Archival box - standard 55-13)
  - Hugh L. Keenleyside - Reports, printed material, letters, 1975; F-55-15-0-0-54 (Archival box - standard 55-14)
  - Grace McCarthy - Letters, printed material. Letters from: Grace McCarthy, 1975; F-55-15-0-0-55 (Archival box - standard 55-14)
  - Order of St. John - Letters, list. Letters from: John Cumberford, 1975; F-55-15-0-0-56 (Archival box - standard 55-14)
  - Social Credit--Election - Letters, telegrams, pamphlets, press release, speech. Letters from: George Mussallem, A.Z. Wozny, Grace McCarthy, Iqbal Sara, Brian Casey, Allie Eddy, Gordon M. Shrum, J.R. Hargen, Margaret J. Dwinell, D.K. Travers, Jerome A. Mark, Clare Brynjolfson, Jerry Seaman, Mary E. Marrs, Beatrice Hughes, K. McClary, Velma Sanders, J. Page, R. Wadsworth, Frank P. Bernard, George E. Anderson, 1975 - 1976; F-55-15-0-0-57 (Archival box - standard 55-14)
  - Sympathy - Letters, card. Letters from: Lila Chinnick, Einar M. Gunderson, 1975; F-55-15-0-0-58 (Archival box - standard 55-14)
  - Who's Who - Letters, biographical note. Letters from: Peter G.C. Jackson, 1975; F-55-15-0-0-59 (Archival box - standard 55-14)
  - Birthday - Letters, cards, telegrams. Letters from: Margaret Sawyer, Iqbal Sara, 1976; F-55-15-0-0-60 (Archival box - standard 55-14)
  - General Correspondence - Letters. Letters from: Anne M. Harris, W.H. Nevin, A.Z. Wozny, C.J. Brush, Paul Martin, R.H.B. Ker, D.V. George, Don Wall, Norman Cribbens, 1976; F-55-15-0-0-61 (Archival box - standard 55-14)
  - General Correspondence - Letters, invitations. Letters from: P.H. Gallagher, Anthony St. John-McGill, C.J. Fiala, Charles Hou, Vernon A. Wiedrich, Raymond [store employee], Kenneth M. Oku, Stanley F. Smith, Linda M. Morris, 1976; F-55-15-0-0-62 (Archival box - standard 55-14)
  - General Correspondence - Letters, memoranda, pamphlet. Letters from: John R. Chalk, Norman Cribbens, Henry Wassmuth, Jim Muise, Peter S. Hyndman, John R. Hecht, Gertie Goffinet, Peter N. Munoz, Fred Hill, Paul Findley, R.H.B. Ker, Wesley P. Munsie, Marcie Morlensen, 1976; F-55-15-0-0-63 (Archival box - standard 55-14)
  - General Correspondence - Letters. Letters from: Julie Rathgeber, Mrs. Charles Adshead, Herta Jofs, 1976; F-55-15-0-0-64 (Archival box - standard 55-14)
  - General Correspondence - Letters, invitations, pamphlet, newspaper clipping. Letters from: Norman Cribbens, Clarence A. White, J.H. Mortimer-Lamb, G.S. Deol, Eleanor L. Hadley, John Roland, 1976; F-55-15-0-0-65 (Archival box - standard 55-14)
  - General Correspondence - Letters, cards. Letters from: D.E. Roberts, Jan Corba, William Clancey, F.H. Jameson, H. Bitterman, Raymond [store employee], Gary Bannerman, Ian Danvers, B. Hultgren, 1976; F-55-15-0-0-66 (Archival box - standard 55-14)
  - General Correspondence - Letters. Letters from: Fred Hill, Stanley F. Smith, Charles A. Drozdzik, 1976; F-55-15-0-0-67 (Archival box - standard 55-14)
  - General Correspondence - Letters, newspaper clipping. Letters from: Patrick L. McGeer, Norman Cribbens, Peter S. Hyndman, Robert L. Fitzhenny, Garde B. Gardon, Nina Fash, Gordon E. Taylor, John S. Catchpole, 1976; F-55-15-0-0-68 (Archival box - standard 55-14)
  - General Correspondence - Letters, pamphlets. Letters from: Lila Chinnick, R.N. Busch, Walter T. Boyce, Paul Martin, M. Lockhart, Denis G.J. Humphries, Scott Dixon, Ray G. Williston, Paul Cassidy, L.J. Wallace, Len Corben, 1976; F-55-15-0-0-69 (Archival box - standard 55-15)
  - General Correspondence - Letters. Letters from: Henry G. Hudel, M.F. Smith, Leona Doduk, David J. Mitchell, Robert M. Strachan, Robert E. Sommers, Donna Charles, Keith Davies, C.R. Walrod, Perry H. Butler, Francis Nathan Milton, Ernie Les Plant, Gary Bannerman, William T. Straith, Mark Jan Vrem, Anna May Charles, John Cumberford, 1976; F-55-15-0-0-70 (Archival box - standard 55-15)
  - General Correspondence - Letters. Letters from: Dorothy Petapiece, John R. Matheson, Yvette Loiselle, Friedrich Niederl, Thomas Ostrom Enders, 1976; F-55-15-0-0-71 (Archival box - standard 55-15)
  - General Correspondence - Letters, cards. Letters from: Frank M. McMahon, Christopher Richardson, W.H. Culbert, Lillian Hunter, Ralph C. Pike, Frank Raffa, F.E. Wright, Norman Cribbens, Margaret A. Duddy, Judith Richard, C.H. Wills, Charles Lakes, 1976; F-55-15-0-0-72 (Archival box - standard 55-15)
  - General Correspondence - Letters, cards. Letters from: Ray G. Williston, Kelvin Beck, John Luten, Derek A. Inman, Ralph C. Pike, Arthur Fouks, T.C. McLaughlin, 1976; F-55-15-0-0-73 (Archival box - standard 55-15)
  - General Correspondence - Letters, cards. Letters from: J.W. Huff, Frank McNair, G.S. Bryson, 1976; F-55-15-0-0-74 (Archival box - standard 55-15)
  - Get Well Cards - Letters from: J. Stuart Keate, Robert W. Bonner, 1976; F-55-15-0-0-75 (Archival box - standard 55-15)
  - Get Well Cards - Letters from: Ted Freedy, H.L. Straight, Gordon M. Shrum, Ray G. Williston, Stuart Fleming, Monica Baker, G.V. Thompson, H.R. McDiarmid, 1976; F-55-15-0-0-76 (Archival box - standard 55-15)
  - Get Well Cards - Letters from: Grace McCarthy, David J. Mitchell, George Simone, 1976; F-55-15-0-0-77 (Archival box - standard 55-15)
  - Get Well Cards, 1976; F-55-15-0-0-78 (Archival box - standard 55-15)
  - Get Well Cards - Letters from: Douglas A. Moore, 1976; F-55-15-0-0-79 (Archival box - standard 55-16)
  - Get Well Cards - Letters from: Jim Kennedy, Isabelle Kennedy, Frank Bernard, Artie Bernard, Clarence A. White, Jack Webster, P. Sherman, G.S. Bryson, 1976; F-55-15-0-0-80 (Archival box - standard 55-16)
  - Get Well Cards - Letters from: Waldo Skillings, Peter S. Hyndman, Joseph H. Cohen, Dan Ekman, 1976; F-55-15-0-0-81 (Archival box - standard 55-16)
  - Get Well Cards - Letters from: E. George MacMinn, Bill Atkinson, 1976; F-55-15-0-0-82 (Archival box - standard 55-16)
  - Get Well Cards - Letters from: Einar M. Gunderson, Paul Manning, 1976; F-55-15-0-0-83 (Archival box - standard 55-16)
  - Get Well Cards - Letters from: H.V. Acland, Eva Dolan, 1976; F-55-15-0-0-84 (Archival box - standard 55-16)
  - Get Well Cards - Letters from: Muni S. Evers, J.M. Pierce, 1976; F-55-15-0-0-85 (Archival box - standard 55-16)
  - Get Well Cards - Letters from: Dorothy Gristwood, John R. Nicholson, T.E. Windt, 1976; F-55-15-0-0-86 (Archival box - standard 55-16)
  - Get Well Cards - Letters from: Simma Holt, Robert Middleton, Frank Raffa, R. Jeffels, 1976; F-55-15-0-0-87 (Archival box - standard 55-16)
  - Get Well Cards, 1976; F-55-15-0-0-88 (Archival box - standard 55-16)
  - Get Well Cards - Letters from: Cora Bennett Macaulay, H.L. Straight, Walter C. Koerner, 1976; F-55-15-0-0-89 (Archival box - standard 55-16)
  - Get Well Cards - Letters from: James Wickert, 1976; F-55-15-0-0-90 (Archival box - standard 55-17)
  - Get Well Cards, 1976; F-55-15-0-0-91 (Archival box - standard 55-17)
  - Get Well Cards, 1976; F-55-15-0-0-92 (Archival box - standard 55-17)
  - Get Well Cards - Letters from: Jack Wasserman, 1976; F-55-15-0-0-93 (Archival box - standard 55-17)
  - Get Well Cards - Letters from: Keith Davies, 1976; F-55-15-0-0-94 (Archival box - standard 55-17)
  - John R. Hecht - Letters, newspaper clippings, program. Letters from: John R. Hecht, B. Wiese, 1976; F-55-15-0-0-95 (Archival box - standard 55-17)
  - Hold File - Letters, notice. Letters from: Arthur D. Cameron, Dieter O. Schwetz, Don Culley, 1976; F-55-15-0-0-96 (Archival box - standard 55-17)
  - Grace McCarthy - Letters, newspaper clippings, printed material. Letters from: Grace McCarthy, 1976; F-55-15-0-0-97 (Archival box - standard 55-17)
  - Media - Letters. Letters from: Roy Jacques, Joan Short, Gary Bannerman, Arden Ostrander, Bob Mackin, 1976; F-55-15-0-0-98 (Archival box - standard 55-17)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1976; F-55-15-0-0-99 (Archival box - standard 55-17)
  - Order of Canada - Letters, list. Letters from: Esmond Butler, 1976; F-55-15-0-0-100 (Archival box - standard 55-17)
  - Order of Canada - Letters, telegrams, cards. Letters from: Raymond Perrault, John Evans, J.V. Clyne, Gordon F. Gibson, Roger de C. Nantel, Paul Martin, 1976; F-55-15-0-0-101 (Archival box - standard 55-17)
  - Robert E. Sommers - Letters, newspaper clippings. Letters from: Robert E. Sommers, 1976; F-55-15-0-0-102 (Archival box - standard 55-17)
  - Weird Letters - Letters. Letters from: Edward W. Green, A. Nolte, H. Batison, 1976; F-55-15-0-0-103 (Archival box - standard 55-17)
  - Agent General - Letter, advertisement. Letters from: L.J. Wallace, 1977; F-55-15-0-0-104 (Archival box - standard 55-18)
  - May Bennett - Letters. Letters from: David Skillings, 1977; F-55-15-0-0-105 (Archival box - standard 55-18)
  - B.C. Railway Royal Commission.- Letters, statement. Letters from: Lloyd G. McKenzie, Martin R. Taylor, Allisen Croft, 1977; F-55-15-0-0-106 (Archival box - standard 55-18)
  - B.C. Railway Royal Commission--J.S. Broadbent - Submission, 1977; F-55-15-0-0-107 (Archival box - standard 55-18)
  - Birthday - Cards, letters, 1977; F-55-15-0-0-108 (Archival box - standard 55-18)
  - Birthday - Cards, letters. Letters from: Keith Davies, 1977; F-55-15-0-0-109 (Archival box - standard 55-18)
  - Canada--Five Region Plan - Letters, press release, map. Letters from: Ray Gasby, E. Buterman, 1977; F-55-15-0-0-110 (Archival box - standard 55-18)
  - General Correspondence - Letters, newspaper clippings, pamphlet. Letters from: Neville A. Millar, Howard T. Mitchell, Anna May Charles, Charles Frick, H.S. Doman, 1977; F-55-15-0-0-111 (Archival box - standard 55-18)
  - General Correspondence - Letters, newspaper clippings. Letters from: D. Acheson, Dorothy I. Stubbs, Ruth Galics, T.H. Meagher, William Murphy, Avraham Harman, D.C. Fillmore, Keith Davies, Frank S. Dingman, 1977; F-55-15-0-0-112 (Archival box - standard 55-18)
  - General Correspondence - Letters. Letters from: Hilda Harrington, M. Gatey, J.H. McIntosh, Norman Cribbens, Lynn Sutherford, Paul Manning, Winnifred Bodkin, Harold Elliott, Alfred Mutchnik, Robert W. Bonner, 1977; F-55-15-0-0-113 (Archival box - standard 55-18)
  - General Correspondence - Letters, newsletter. Letters from: Lyle Kahl, Norman Cribbens, Red Dickson, Frank Jameson, Roger W. Kibble, Helene Dueck, L.J. Wallace, 1977; F-55-15-0-0-114 (Archival box - standard 55-18)
  - General Correspondence - Letters, report. Letters from: Basil T. Richards, Raymond [store employee], L.A. Yellowlees, Patricia J. Jordan, Gilles Caouette, Mary Moon, William Clancey, Augusta Caimmi Lamoureux, Dianne Hartwick, Dereck A. Inman, 1977; F-55-15-0-0-115 (Archival box - standard 55-18)
  - General Correspondence - Letters, article. Letters from: Marianne Macdonald, David Radler, Ken J. Dryborough, Ellen Tattersall-Moses, Leonard C. DeLozier, Doris Bennett, 1977; F-55-15-0-0-116 (Archival box - standard 55-18)
  - General Correspondence - Letters, printed material. Letters from: John R. Hecht, Dianne Hartwick, E.R.F. Dodd, Frank Johnson, Einar M. Gunderson, Raymond Perrault, Frank L. Rogers, G.S. Bryson, Ron Finnigan, Tom Bryden, 1977; F-55-15-0-0-117 (Archival box - standard 55-18)
  - General Correspondence - Letters. Letters from: Clive H. Warren, John Cumberford, George Mussallem, Florence Dickinson, Yvette Laiselle, John Plul, Paul M. Mulvihill, 1977; F-55-15-0-0-118 (Archival box - standard 55-18)
  - General Correspondence - Letters, cards. Letters from: A. Franco, Charles G. Butterworth, Denis G. Humphries, Edward L. Cohen, Robert G. McKay, E.M. Lloyd, J. Frederic Hobson, D.N. Nelson, Richard N. Lillico, Dalton McCarthy, Evan M. Wolfe, Robert I. Fitzhenry, Frank Richter, H.L. Straight, 1977; F-55-15-0-0-119 (Archival box - standard 55-18)
  - General Correspondence - Letters, report. Letters from: Mabel Bates, Peter R. Gook, J.D. Hamm, Sam Bawlf, Les Keen, John R. Hecht, 1977; F-55-15-0-0-120 (Archival box - standard 55-18)
  - General Correspondence - Letters, cards. Letters from: Patricia J. Jordan, Lyle Kahl, C. Gallagher, Robert L. Wenman, Hugh L. Keenleyside, Austin Millar, John Hindle, Michelle Lockhead, Gordon M. Shrum, Kathy Sutherland, Norman Cribbens, James L. O'Dell, Sylvia Richter, Dorothy Carloss, 1977; F-55-15-0-0-121 (Archival box - standard 55-18)
  - Hebrew University - Letters, list. Letters from: Avraham Harman, Morris J. Wosk, 1977; F-55-15-0-0-122 (Archival box - standard 55-18)
  - Insurance - Insurance policy, 1977; F-55-15-0-0-123 (Archival box - standard 55-18)
  - Invitations - Letters, invitations. Letters from: Margaret Mok, John Luton, Judith Richard, Charles Lakes, F.E. Paul, John Cumberford, William C. Gibson, 1977; F-55-15-0-0-124 (Archival box - standard 55-18)
  - Invitations - Letters, invitations. Letters from: Gus Halliday, George Smith, Mark G. Morris, D. Stephenson, E.W. Welpton, R.N. Busch, 1977; F-55-15-0-0-125 (Archival box - standard 55-19)
  - Kiplinger Washington Letter, 1977; F-55-15-0-0-126 (Archival box - standard 55-19)
  - Richard N. Lillico - Letters, card. Letters from: Richard N. Lillico, 1977; F-55-15-0-0-127 (Archival box - standard 55-19)
  - Grace McCarthy - Letters, article, printed material. Letters from: Grace McCarthy, 1977; F-55-15-0-0-128 (Archival box - standard 55-19)
  - Memberships and Passes - Letters. Letters from: B.G. Wilson, C. Gallagher, 1977; F-55-15-0-0-129 (Archival box - standard 55-19)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1977; F-55-15-0-0-130 (Archival box - standard 55-19)
  - Phoenix Medal - Letters. Letters from: A.P. Morley, 1977; F-55-15-0-0-131 (Archival box - standard 55-19)
  - Correspondence--Ted Dixon - Letters, photographs. Letters from: Ted Dixon, 1977; F-55-15-0-0-132 (Archival box - standard 55-19)
  - Correspondence--Jim Ryan - Letters, photographs. Letters from: Jim Ryan, 1977; F-55-15-0-0-133 (Archival box - standard 55-19)
  - Social Credit - Letters, report, telegram. Letters from: Burt Campbell, Peter S. Hyndman, Florence Dickinson, 1977; F-55-15-0-0-134 (Archival box - standard 55-19)
  - Wedding Anniversary - Letters, lists, 1977; F-55-15-0-0-135 (Archival box - standard 55-19)
  - Wedding Anniversary - Letters, list, 1977; F-55-15-0-0-136 (Archival box - standard 55-19)
  - Evan Wolfe - Letters. Letters from: Robert W. Bonner, Evan Wolfe, 1977; F-55-15-0-0-137 (Archival box - standard 55-19)
  - Bank of British Columbia - Letters, interview. Letters from: R.L. Hodgkinson, Lana Man, 1978; F-55-15-0-0-138 (Archival box - standard 55-19)
  - B.C. Government Appointments - Letters, newspaper clipping. Letters from: E.N. Veitch, James R. Chabot, Richard N. Lillico, Grace McCarthy, 1978; F-55-15-0-0-139 (Archival box - standard 55-19)
  - B.C. Railway Royal Commission - Letters, report, editorial. Letters from: Paul M. Mulvihill, Joe Broadbent, Don Phillips, Charles R. MacLean, John R. Matheson, G.S. Bryson, Gary Bannerman, 1978; F-55-15-0-0-140 (Archival box - standard 55-19)
  - Bennett's Stores - Letters [file missing], 1978; F-55-15-0-0-141
  - Bennett's Stores and Apex - Balance sheets, receipts, letters [file missing], 1978; F-55-15-0-0-142
  - Christmas - Letters, cards. Letters from: Einar M. Gunderson, Dianne Hartwick, 1978; F-55-15-0-0-143 (Archival box - standard 55-20)
  - Clubs and Lodges - Letters, receipts. Letters from: J.E. Harsine, David Clayton Ellsworth, 1978; F-55-15-0-0-144 (Archival box - standard 55-20)
  - Croatian Peasant Society - Letters, newspaper clippings, 1978; F-55-15-0-0-145 (Archival box - standard 55-20)
  - Croatian Peasant Society--Bust - Letters. Letters from: Mladen G. Zorkin, 1978; F-55-15-0-0-146 (Archival box - standard 55-20)
  - General Correspondence - Letters, press release. Letters from: Fran Dowie, Charles R. MacLean, Richard N. Lillico, William Vander Zalm, W. Lyding, Fin Thomson, Ian Bain, Andy Stephen, 1978; F-55-15-0-0-147 (Archival box - standard 55-20)
  - General Correspondence - Letters, invitations. Letters from: G.A. McKee, Ruby E. Lidstone, Ann Casselman Paul, Ernest Gibson, Charles Lakes, A.F. Cameron, 1978; F-55-15-0-0-148 (Archival box - standard 55-20)
  - General Correspondence - Letters, invitations. Letters from: Harvey W. Schroeder, 1978; F-55-15-0-0-149 (Archival box - standard 55-20)
  - General Correspondence - Letters, invitations, pamphlet. Letters from: Ross Johnson, Robert Vietus Read, T.H. Peters, Beatrice Eligh, Eugene Forsey, Melvin H. Smith, Bob and Phyllis Maddocks, Mathilda Vennard, Dianne Hartwick, F.M. Sharpe, 1978; F-55-15-0-0-150 (Archival box - standard 55-20)
  - General Correspondence - Letters, telegram, invitation. Letters from: Jack Diamond, A. Petersen, Trevor W. Pilley, John Dodd, Ben Chmelyk, Walter C. Koerner, F.G. Bernie Brauer, 1978; F-55-15-0-0-151 (Archival box - standard 55-20)
  - General Correspondence - Letters, invitation, report. Letters from: Sylvia Dendy, M. Harmer, 1978; F-55-15-0-0-152 (Archival box - standard 55-20)
  - General Correspondence - Letters, pamphlet. Letters from: May Fillmore, Ted Brothers, Frank M. McMahon, 1978; F-55-15-0-0-153 (Archival box - standard 55-20)
  - General Correspondence - Letters, invitations. Letters from: Ray G. Williston, John Johnston, Mona McClelland, 1978; F-55-15-0-0-154 (Archival box - standard 55-20)
  - General Correspondence - Letters, cards. Letters from: Irene Ritchie, Florence Dickinson, Frank Maddern, Gerda Nilsson, May Fillmore, J.H. Fraser, W. Beathie, D.V. Fisher, 1978; F-55-15-0-0-155 (Archival box - standard 55-20)
  - General Correspondence - Letters, essays. Letters from: John E. Wiley, 1978; F-55-15-0-0-156 (Archival box - standard 55-20)
  - Kelowna and District Credit Union - Letters, 1978; F-55-15-0-0-157 (Archival box - standard 55-21)
  - Cora Bennett Macaulay- Article, 1978; F-55-15-0-0-158 (Archival box - standard 55-21)
  - Grace McCarthy - Letters, press release, 1978; F-55-15-0-0-159 (Archival box - standard 55-21)
  - Okanagan Lake Bridge - Memorandum, notes, newspaper clipping, sign, lists, 1978; F-55-15-0-0-160 (Archival box - standard 55-21)
  - Okanagan Lake Bridge - Letters, telegrams. Letters from: Pierre Elliott Trudeau, Otto Lang, 1978; F-55-15-0-0-161 (Archival box - standard 55-21)
  - Okanagan Lake Bridge - Petitions, 1978; F-55-15-0-0-162 (Archival box - standard 55-21)
  - Okanagan Lake Bridge - Petitions, 1978; F-55-15-0-0-163 (Archival box - standard 55-21)
  - Okanagan Lake Bridge - Petitions, 1978; F-55-15-0-0-164 (Archival box - standard 55-21)
  - Seaview Apartments - Letters. Letters from: C.D. Skillings, 1978; F-55-15-0-0-165 (Archival box - standard 55-21)
  - L.J. Wallace - Letters, photograph. Letters from: L.J. Wallace, Richard N. Lillico, 1978; F-55-15-0-0-166 (Archival box - standard 55-21)
  - Evan Wolfe - Letter, 1978; F-55-15-0-0-167 (Archival box - standard 55-21)
  - General Correspondence - Letters, cards. Letters from: Fraser Kelley, Jack McClelland, Nigel H. Gunn, Edward Schreyer, Gary Bannerman, Sarah Glaser, John E. Wiley, C.A. Marshall, G. Blais, Grace McCarthy, G.T. Cameron, Dean F. Mlarjsin, 1978; F-55-15-0-0-168 (Archival box - standard 55-21)
  - Get Well Cards, 1978; F-55-15-0-0-169 (Archival box - standard 55-21)
  - Passes - Letters. Letters from: C. Gallagher, George Wainborn, Stuart Lefeaux, 1978; F-55-15-0-0-170 (Archival box - standard 55-21)
- Memorial, 1947 - 1979; F-55-16; 4 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records relating to Bennett's funeral arrangements, funeral service, memorial service and memorial fund. Included are lists, programs, a press release, letters, notes, newspaper clippings, a folder and pamphlets.
  - Funeral Arrangements - Lists, program, press release, notes, 1979; F-55-16-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 55-21)
  - Correspondence - Letters, programs, 1979; F-55-16-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 55-21)
  - Memorial Clippings - Newspaper Clippings, 1979; F-55-16-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 55-21)
  - Memorial Fund - Folder, pamphlets, 1979; F-55-16-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 55-21)
  - Biographical material, 1947 - 1979; F-55-16-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 55-21)
- Ephemera (personal), 1930 - 1979; F-55-17; 37 cm of textual records; Predominant dates are 1940-1970.
  Series consists of ephemera relating to a variety of personal and official activities. Included are identification cards, a wallet, a ration coupon book, a Bible, greeting cards, publications, pamphlets, a name plate, programs, invitations, menus, place mats, posters, an agreement, a transparency and letter head.
  - Identification Cards, 1940 - 1975; F-55-17-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 55-22)
  - Identification Cards - Wallet, card, 1958; F-55-17-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 55-22)
  - Ration Coupon Book, 1945; F-55-17-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 55-22)
  - Common Prayer Book, F-55-17-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 55-22)
  - Cards Received, 1952 - 1968; F-55-17-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 55-22)
  - Cards to be Sent, F-55-17-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 55-22)
  - Speech., 1967; F-55-17-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 55-22)
  - Pamphlets, 1956; F-55-17-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 55-22)
  - Name Plate, F-55-17-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 55-22)
  - Programs, 1948 - 1959; F-55-17-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 55-22)
  - Programs, 1960 - 1964; F-55-17-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 55-22)
  - Programs, 1965 - 1966; F-55-17-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 55-22)
  - Programs, 1967; F-55-17-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 55-22)
  - Programs, 1968 - 1969; F-55-17-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 55-23)
  - Programs, 1970; F-55-17-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 55-23)
  - Programs, 1971; F-55-17-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 55-23)
  - Programs, 1972 - 1974; F-55-17-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 55-23)
  - Programs--Premiers' Conferences, 1961; F-55-17-0-0-18 (Archival box - standard 55-23)
  - Invitations, 1940 - 1950; F-55-17-0-0-19 (Archival box - standard 55-23)
  - Invitations, 1960 - 1969; F-55-17-0-0-20 (Archival box - standard 55-23)
  - Invitations, 1970 - 1979; F-55-17-0-0-21 (Archival box - standard 55-23)
  - Menus, 1951 - 1960; F-55-17-0-0-22 (Archival box - standard 55-23)
  - Menus, 1961 - 1969; F-55-17-0-0-23 (Archival box - standard 55-23)